<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Impossibility is only the beginning</title>
    <link>https://adamshimi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Impossibility is only the beginning</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://adamshimi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://adamshimi.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamshimi.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a PhD student in theoretical computer science in Toulouse, France. My subject is the theorey of distributed computing, more specifically the use of rounds to abstract away fault and communication models.
My other interests also include effective altruism, AI safety, literature, Rust and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://adamshimi.github.io/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamshimi.github.io/posts/</guid>
      <description>In construction&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>https://adamshimi.github.io/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamshimi.github.io/papers/</guid>
      <description>Up-to-date list of published and submitted papers, complementing my dblp profile.
 Derivation of Heard-Of Predicates From Elementary Behavioral Patterns, with Aurélie Hurault and Philippe Quéinnec. In submission, with preprint available. K set-agreement bounds in round-based models through combinatorial topology, with Armando Castañeda. In submission, with preprint available. The Splendors and Miseries of Rounds. Published in SIGACT News Distributed Computing Column, issue September 2019. My version. Characterizing Asynchronous Message-Passing Models Through Rounds, with Aurélie Hurault and Philippe Quéinnec.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://adamshimi.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adamshimi.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>All the classes I taught, with some slides (in french)
 Teaching Assistant and Labs in &amp;ldquo;Operating Systems&amp;rdquo; class Teaching Assistant and Labs in &amp;ldquo;Concurrent Programming&amp;rdquo; class Lab Assistant in &amp;ldquo;Functional Programming&amp;rdquo; class Lecturer in &amp;ldquo;Introduction to Computation Complexity&amp;rdquo; class  First Lecture (On time complexity, P and NP) : Du calcul efficace à la vérification efficace Second Lecture (On space complexity) : La puissance de l&amp;rsquo;espace : de la connectivité aux jeux Third Lecture (On probabilistic time complexity and interactive protocols): L&amp;rsquo;aléa du calcul et la vérification interactive    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>